# **Chicco Moshe Serby**

Address:

Netanya, Israel

Phone:

+972 (0)58 5313233

**Email:** 

ChiccoMoshe@gmail.com

**PORTFOLIO** 

### Summary

Junior Web Developer - Full Stack.

Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming skills including:

HTML5, CSS3 (responsive design), Node.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, React (Classes & Hooks), Redux, jQuery, rest API, MongoDB (Mongoose), MySQL, Socket.io, PL-SQL, OOP, C++.

### Experience

### **Technical Support Specialist** - 01/2019 - today **Checker Software Systems Ltd**, Israel

- Cooperate with designers and development department in order to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences with the software.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Providing answers, services and technical solutions through the software and support tickets system.
- Training new and existing users and demos for new customers.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Writing / updating CSS files for dashboards and surveys design.

### PL-SQL developer, Oracle App - 01/2013 - 01/2016

#### Advantech Ltd, Israel

- Receive software requirements specification and execution as required.
- The job mainly involved writing SQL queries, oracle DB.
- Main projects:
  - Bar Ilan University, ongoing maintenance
  - Soda Club support, system upgrade and

## **Chicco Moshe Serby**

Address:

Netanya, Israel

Phone:

+972 (0)58 5313233

Email:

ChiccoMoshe@gmail.com

**PORTFOLIO** 

#### Education

Full Stack Course. (07/19 - today)

Interbit.

B.SC in Computer Science. (2009-2012)

**HIT Israel** 

### Skill Highlights

- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Ability to work under pressure and diligence
- Creative design
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- High self-learning ability

### Languages

Hebrew - A1

English - A2

### Certifications

**Programming Languages:** 

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery, rest API, React, MongoDB (Mongoose), Socket.IO, PL-SQL, OOP, C++.

### Relevant Links



Recommendations will be sent upon request.